

CONTACT



www.robertgregg.co.uk

PRO SKILLS



PERSONALITY

Motivated	
Creative	
Analytical	
Team Work	
Attitude	
Problem Solving	

ROBERT GREGG

Frontend Software/Web Developer

I have a passion for coding and have enjoyed working on a wide range of projects. My past experience is mainly in front end development however I enjoy learning the new skills required in every project. I enjoy both being a part of a synergistic team and/or working alone.

EXPERIENCE

FEB 2021 - PRESENT

Software Devloper (mid level)

THE IBI GROUP

- ReactJS Angular Typescript Dev ops
 Github FrontEnd APIs UI/UX
- Various projects involving google maps & working with masses of data coming from or going to the maps. Building Dashboards, connecting front to backend, adhering to best practices, reusable components (functional and also class based with an object Orientatedapproach). Devops / Github for Cl. Working on my own and in small / large teams.

OCT 2019 - OCT 2020

Junior Software Developer

SWITCHPLANE

- Agile/ScrumJavascriptCSS3HTML
- SourceTree PHP UI

Building widgets/adding functionality to existing widgets on client sites and switchplane projects. Creating landing pages from designs, website analysis/overhauls, fixing bugs

JAN 2006 - AUG 2020

Director

SS4A/S3 STUDIOS

Digital Marketing
 Adobe Suite
 HTML
 CSS3
 Wordpress
 Managing stafff

Business owner involved in all aspects of running successful self employed businesses. Front of house, behind the scenes, tech man, customer service - wearing all hats.

MAY 2018 - SEPT 2020

Freelance Web Designer/Developer

VARIOUS

HTML CSS3
 Wordpress
 Managing clients

Liaising with clients to create desired websites. Updates. Bugs.

TRAINING

I have been in the development world since 2005, however 2016 was where my journey took center stage. My portfolio website contains many apps, mainly built with React, Vanilla Javascript and more working with API data. The apps range from Linkedln/Facebook/Whatsapp clones using firebase authentication, as well as an Amazon clone with full payment processing. Since my knowledge has deepend ion React, Javascript, OOP and I have now worked on large Angular projects.

2019 - PRESENT

Home Learning

NOV 2020

Creative Process

2002 - 2005

University of West London

VARIOUS

Tutorials to help with my portfolio website and many apps that are present there. Freecodecamp, Pluralsite, codeacademy, frontend Masters, Udemy (various), Azure fundamentals, YouTube (various), and more...

BSC LEVEL 4

Diploma in Software Development Methodologies

BA HONS MULTIMEDIA COMPUTING

Photoshop, HTML< MySQL, Javascript, Java

REFERENCES

Joel Fielder

Switchplane

joel@switchplane.com

Daniel Ceresia

The Little Design Group

dan@thelittlewineguy.com

David Hall

The Cloudy Group david@cloudyit.co.uk